# GAURI SHANKAR SHARMA

# Studying BSc (Hons)Computing

**2**: 9816346714,

🔀: gaurisharma358@gmail.com

**9:** Sundarharaincha-1, Morang, Province-1

## **Personal Profile**

A confident Django web developer with more than 6 months of working experience along with a core skill of python and java programming language. Along with the SQL and NoSQL database management knowledge, I am always enthusiastic about enhancing my skills in the IT field as much as possible.

With my previous working experience as Cashier, photo and video editor, and web designer, I have developed a friendly and approachable persona with the customer which gives me more encouragement to apply for high-level posts.

Work Experience		
February 2017 - August 2017	Cashier - Gorkha Department Store, Biratchowk Branch Morang, Province-I	
	<ul> <li>Registering sales by scanning items, itemizing and totaling customer's purchases, and processing return transactions.</li> </ul>	
March 2020 - January 2021	Photo and video editor - Utama Photo Studio Morang, Province-1	
	<ul> <li>Photoshop editing for passport size photo, video editing for marriages video.</li> </ul>	
January 2021 - Till Date	Junior front end web developer - Uplift Company	
	Kathmandu, Bagmati Province	
	<ul> <li>Front-end designing for websites with Django.</li> </ul>	

Education	
April 2016 - April 2017	SEE, Shree Janata Secondary School Morang, Province-I.
July 2017 - May 2019	<ul> <li>Completed With a 3.55 GPA.</li> <li>+2 In science faculty, Sukuna Secondary School Morang, Province-1.</li> </ul>
	• Completed With a 3.72 GPA.
September 2019 - Till Date	BSc (Hons) Computing, Softwarica College Kathmandu, Bagmati Province.
	• Completed let Samester With 74.07 % 2nd Samester V

• Completed 1st Semester With 74.07 %, 2nd Semester With 71.5 %, 3rd Semester With 80.75 %, and Just Completed 4rth Semester.

Skills		
Python	Java	HTML, CSS, JavaScript
Bootstrap	Django	SQL
MongoDB, Graph DB	Tableau Data Visualization	Adobe XD Prototype Design
Mongozz, Gruph ZZ		
Language		
Nepali	Khawas	English

### **Education Awards and Honors**

- **Shivprasad Ghimire Smriti Award, 2019:** Awarded along with 10,000 rupees by Indrapur Jesij for completing class 12 in science faculty with the highest GPA of 3.78.
- **SEE highest scorer certificate, 2017:** Awarded by Shree Janata Secondary school for completing SEE examination with the highest GPA of 3.55.
- Class 6 first student certificate, 2014: Awarded by Education Board Community Dulari Area for scoring highest marks in the annual examination of class 6 conducted by Dulari Examination Board.

### **HOBBIES**

- Photo
- Video Editing
- Supervising
- Video Gaming
- Yoga and Exercise
- Dancing